yotify.com 2015-12-28

# Yotify Privacy Policy

|  |   
---|---|---  
  
Yotify Privacy Policy

branchnext, Inc. (“branchnext”) owns and operates the website located at: [yotify.com](http://www.yotify.com/) (the “Service”). The following outlines the privacy policies adopted by branchnext in its operation of the Service (the “Privacy Policy”).

##  INFORMATION GATHERING AND USAGE

  * When you register for the Service you are asked for information such as your name, and email address.
  * branchnext uses collected information exclusively for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

##  COOKIES

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to use the Yotify Service.
  * We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your Yotify Account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

##  DATA STORAGE

branchnext uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Service. Although branchnext owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Service, you retain all rights to your data.

##  DISCLOSURE

branchnext may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances.

branchnext collects the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregates information on what pages consumers access or visit, and any information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information branchnext collects is used to improve the Service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you have requested, when branchnext has your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Yotify Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law, including compliance with subpoenas.
  * branchnext transfers information about you if branchnext is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, branchnext will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##  CHANGES

branchnext may periodically update the Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

##  QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support at yotify dot com or by mail at:   
branchnext 912 Cole Street #174, San Francisco, CA 94117 USA
